Guide to the Nicole Di Bona Peterson Collection of Advertising Cookbooks, 1850s-2000s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University, Durham, N.C., USA
- American Cookbooks 1930s, 8
  - Sweet Secrets by Kathryn Ward, circa 1930s (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0357)
    Company: Oelerich & Berry Company
    Product: Oelerich syrup
  - Sweetose Best for Cooking, Baking, Canning, Preserving, Freezing Fruits, circa 1938 (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0358)
    Product: Sweetose syrup
  - Modern Menus, circa 1930s (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0359)
    Product: G.E. electric refrigerator, Premier Duplex floor cleaner, Philco radio
  - Use of Gerber's Strained Vegetables in Therapeutic Diets, 1933 (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0360)
    Company: Fremont Canning Company
    Product: Gerber's strained vegetables
    Note: includes health, diet information, bibliography
  - One Hundred Dainty Desserts with Cream of Chocolate, circa 1930s (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0361)
    Note: collection of recipes from a prize competition, with additional recipes by the judges (Mrs. Sarah Tyson Rorer, Miss Imogene C. Belden). Includes 'beverages for the sick'
  - Milk for Drinking as You Like It, 1930 (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0364)
  - This New Freedom, 1931 (Box A17, Item 1930sA-0367)
    Product: KLIM
  - This Sweet Chocolate is the Champ for Those who Picnic, Hike, or Camp!, circa 1930s (Box A18, Item 1930sA-0367)
  - 100 Delicious Lime Recipes, 1932 (Box A19, Item 1930sA-0368)
    Company: Caribbean Limes Association
    Product: limes
  - (No Title), 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0001)
    Company: Munson G. Shaw Company, Inc.
    Product: Noilly Prat Vermouth
    Note: Photographs, history, characteristics, uses
  - 9 High Spots for 9 Meals with Swans Down Cake Flour, 1936 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0002)
    Note: Red headings, small, fold-out pamphlet
  - $3334 in Cash Prizes!, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0003)
    Note: Color illustrations, Prize contest for naming butter sponge cake, Betty Crocker
  - $10, 002 in Cash Prizes for Naming 'Things-to-Bake' in these Recipe Folders, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0004)
    Note: Prize contest for naming 'Things-to-Bake' including lemon pie and orange rolls, Betty Crocker
  - The Art of Serving Bread, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0005)
    Note: black-and-white illustrations, color illustrations on inside of cover, tips and household hints included
  - Bond Bread Cook Book, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0006)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, color illustration of bread types on back
  - …Every 'Balanced' recipe has an Official OK, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0007)
    Company: Pillsbury Cooking Service
    Note: Four/five types of flour, letter from Mary Ellis Ames, write-in for a new recipe book
  - Foods Men Rave About!, 1936 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0008)
    Note: Betty Crocker recipes, coupon for Wm. Rogers & Son silverware included
  - How Would You Like to Win $3, 000?, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0009)
    Note: Contest to name Bob Crane's favorite dessert
  - Maca Made' Tested Bake-Day Suggestions, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0010)
    Note: black-and-white pictures, color illustrations, intro, hints (end)
  - Modern Menus Cakes that Never Fall, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0011)
    Note: Recipes, Ads for Philco radio and Miller sunlamp
  - New Party Cakes For All Occasions, 1931 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0012)
    Note: Betty Crocker, color illustrations
  - Practical Recipes from the Globe Mills, 1931 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0013)
    Note: Handwritten Spanish rice and pie crust recipes in Memoranda section at back
  - Program of the Leader-Republican-Herald Cooking School, 1934 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0014)
    Company: Multiple
    Product: Multiple
    Note: 13 merchants and manufacturers cooperating to make cooking school a success, information slip removed
  - Recipes for Clinton Corn Starch, 1937 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0015)
    Company: Clinton Company
    Product: Clinton Corn Starch
    Note: 19 recipes
  - Recipes for Delicious Varieties of Bread…, 1931 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0016)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, helpful hints
  - (No Title), 1931 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0017)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, how-to instructions with photographs
  - Tested Cherry Recipes, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0018)
    Product: Red pie cherries
    Note: Picture of cherry pie, 7 cherry recipes
  - Yukon Best Cook Book, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0019)
    Company: Yukon Mill & Grain Company
    Product: Yukon flour
    Note: Non-colored illustrations
  - Baking Soda.. A Friend in Need, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0020)
    Note: information on using baking soda to gargle, for scalds and burns, for indigestion, and Castor Oil sandwich
  - Cleansing Healps Washing Soda, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0021)
    Note: Small illustrations, instructions for how to use in various parts of home
  - Good Things To Eat, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0022)
    Note: Knitted-looking cover, color photographs, recipes, more uses for baking soda
  - Good Things To Eat, Tested Recipes, 1936 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0023)
    Note: photographs, facts regarding flour, kitchen tested methods
  - Make Finer Biscuits They Cost So Little thanks to Calumet's Double-Action!, 1938 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0024)
    Note: A few black-and-white pictures, information and advertising for Calumet
  - Rumford New Use Cook Book, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0025)
    Note: Page of pictures from various recipes
  - How to Make Good Coffee, 1937 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0026)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, instructions for various processes of brewing coffee
  - Food from your Coffee Pot, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0027)
    Note: Three drawings, instructions for making good coffee
  - Home Canning Guide by Kerr, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0028)
    Product: Kerr fruit jars
    Note: black-and-white and color illustrations (cover), steps in canning with illustrations
  - Speaking of Jars Jams, Relishes and things, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0029)
    Product: Kerr jars
    Note: Illustrations and pictures, uses the alphabet to describe Kerr jars, recipes on final page
  - 16 Delicious Chocolate Recipes, 1938 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0030)
    Note: Illustration on cover, small fold-out pamphlet
  - Delicious Recipes including Toll House Chocolate Cookies, 1934 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0031)
    Company: Lamont, Corliss & Company
    Product: Nestlé's Semi-Sweet Chocolate
    Note: Color photograph on cover, illustrations on first and last page
  - Hershey's Index Recipe Book, 1934 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0032)
    Product: Hershey's Chocolate
    Note: Color illustrations, the art of cake making
  - Delicious Desserts and Candies, 1931 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0033)
    Product: Various extracts (i.e. vanilla, almond, etc.)
    Note: Color illustrations on inside of cover, Introduction
  - It Tastes Like it Sounds, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0034)
    Company: Nalley's Inc.
    Product: Tang
    Note: Green, lettuce background, The Story of Tang
  - McNess' Cook Book, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0035)
    Note: Cake backing secrets, Foreign recipes, Popular American recipes
  - White House Coffee Cups, Their Historic Associations, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0036)
    Company: Dwinell-Wright Company
    Product: White House coffee and tea
    Note: Color and black-and-white illustrations, brief biographies of all of the First Ladies with pictures of coffee cups
  - A New Flavor Delight, 1933 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0037)
    Note: black-and-white drawings at the beginning of each section
  - New Magic in the Kitchen, circa 1930s (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0038)
    Product: Sweetened Condensed Milk
    Note: Color illustrations, Includes measuring instructions
  - (No Title on front) 100 Selected Dried Fruit Recipes, 1939 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0039)
    Company: California Dried Fruit Research Institute
    Product: Dried fruit
    Note: black-and-white photographs, information next to each recipe, nutritional value and story of dried fruits
  - Prunes for Epicures, 35 Intriguing Recipes, 1933 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0040)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, includes the correct way to prepare prunes
  - Royal Desserts and Salads, 1935 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0041)
    Product: Royal Brand gelatins
    Note: Color and black-and-white photographs and illustrations, how-to guide with pics
  - Here's Your Bond Bread Sandwich Chart, 1936 (Box B02, Item 1930sB-0042)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, color illustrations, helpful tricks, various sandwich recipes
  - How to Use the Grayson Oven Control, 1937 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0043)
    Company: Grayson Heat Control, Ltd.
    Product: Grayson Oven Control
    Note: Includes tables and diagrams
  - Frigidaire Recipe Book, 1931 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0044)
    Product: Frigidaire appliances
    Note: black-and-white pictures of appliances and/or women, newspaper cutout, handwritten recipe
  - Short Course in Modern Gas Cookery, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0045)
    Company: Gaffers & Sattler
    Product: Automatic Gas Range
    Note: Charts for time and temperature, broiling, baking, cooking suggestion
  - Westinghouse Automatic Electric Range Book, 1937 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0046)
    Product: Automatic Electric Range
    Note: Spiral bound, black-and-white photographs, various tables
  - 60 Ways to Serve Ham, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0047)
    Product: Armour's ham
    Note: Color illustrations, chart on what to serve with Armour's ham
  - Sea Food Recipes Sam's Fish Market, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0048)
    Company: Newport Harbor Publishing Company
    Product: Sam's Fish Market
    Note: Instructions for preparing and cooking a variety of seafood
  - Appetizers Bridge Sandwiches Cocktail Canapes, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0049)
    Note: Color illustrations, small pamphlet, Descriptions of appetizer types
  - Cup Reading The Ancient Art of Foretelling the Future, 1934 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0050)
    Company: Salada Tea Company, Inc.
    Product: Salada Tea
    Note: Black, white, and green illustrations, instructions for preparing and reading tea leaves
  - Cupid's Book, 1935 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0051)
    Company: Kiessling Publishing Company
    Product: multiple products (esp. Ghirardelli's Chocolate)
    Note: For a bride, black-and-white photographs and illustrations, tables and diagrams
  - Foods Men Rave About by Betty Crocker, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0052)
    Company: General Mills/Betty Crocker
    Note: Coupon detached, illustration of Betty Crocker on front
  - Golden--V Vitamin Recipes, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0053)
    Product: Golden-V Vitamin Milk
    Note: Non-color illustrations, chart with nutritional advantages of vitamin milk
  - The Hostess Entertains, 1935 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0054)
    Company: Consumers Ice and Cold Storage Company
    Product: Ice refrigerator
    Note: black-and-white photographs of food, Ice refrigerator, woman (Nina G. Abbey?)
  - My Best Recipes by Mary Hale Martin, 1934 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0055)
    Product: Multiple Libby products
    Note: black-and-white photographs at beginning, color photographs throughout
  - Peanut Butter Read These Simple Facts about Vitamins and Vitamin D, 1932 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0056)
    Company: Seeman Brothers, Inc.
    Product: Vitamized Peanut Butter
    Note: information about vitamins in product, 5 recipes on reverse
  - Sandwich Secrets Rich in Vitality Values, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0057)
    Company: Anchor Bread Company
    Product: Butter cream bread
    Note: black-and-white photographs of food, family eating a picnic
  - Foods Made Famous at the World's Fair, 1939 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0058)
    Company: Julia Lee Wright
    Note: Worldwide cuisine, color cover, orange illustrations
  - Menus and Recipes, 1931 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0059)
    Company: Safeway Stores, Inc.
    Note: Guides for planning and shopping, Meals laid out for you
  - The Art of Cooking and Serving, with 549 Tested Crisco Recipes, 1937 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0060)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, color illustrations, charts, instructions for houses with and without servants
  - Staley's Approved Recipes, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0061)
    Product: Staley's products
    Note: Color illustrations, black-and-white picture of Grace Viall Gray
  - What Shall I Cook Today?- 124 thrifty, healthful tested recipes, 1930 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0062)
    Note: black-and-white and color pictures, color comic on front and back covers
  - Recipes, 1931 (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0063)
    Product: KitchenAid electrical food preparer
    Note: black-and-white illustrations, diagram of appliance, attachments, accessories, general instructions
  - The Heinz Salad Book, circa 1930s (Box B03, Item 1930sB-0064)
    Product: Multiple Heinz products
    Note: black-and-white pictures outlining ingredients, steps, and end results, color photograph in center of all Heinz products
  - Si, si, Lady, Thees Drink Taste So Good' Daiquiri Cocktail as it's made in the tropics with Ronrico Puerto Rican Rum, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0001)
    Company: Ronrico Corporation
    Product: Ronrico Rum
  - Wine Handbook, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0002)
  - 15 Ways to a Man's Heart, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0003)
  - 16 Delightful New Recipes, created to please discriminating Southern palates, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0004)
    Note: fold out pamphlet, black-and-white pictures, recipes developed and proved by Mary Ellis Ames (Director of Pillsbury Cooking Service)
  - Argo Corn Starch for Delicious Desserts, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0005)
    Company: Argo Corn Starch
    Product: Argo Corn Starch
    Note: color illustrations on front cover
  - Betty Crocker's $25, 000 Recipe Set No. 3, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0006)
  - Betty Crocker's $25, 000 Recipe Set No. 4, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0007)
  - Cream Soups, Sauces, Entrees, Salads, Hot Breads, Pies, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0008)
    Product: Staley corn starch, breakfast syrup, Golden Table Syrup, Crystal White Syrup
  - Hostess Dessert Fingers, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0009)
    Company: Hostess
  - Mother's Pride Cookbook, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0010)
    Product: (Not listed)
    Note: black-and-white illustration on cover, various recipes/information, inserted recipe for apple cake and other various ads
  - New 'A1' Waffle & Pancake Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0011)
    Product: A1' Pancake and Waffle Flour, Oil, Flour
  - New Cake Secrets, 1931 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0012)
  - New Editions of Old Favorites Men Like, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0013)
    Company: Betty Crocker
  - New Editions of Old Favorites Men Like, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0014)
  - Pillsbury's Cookery Club, 1935 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0015)
    Note: created by Mary Ellis Ames, black-and-white pictures and illustrations, coupon for monthly bulletin
  - Practical Recipes from the Globe Mills, 1932 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0016)
    Product: Globe 'A1' Products
    Note: color cover and back
  - Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0017)
    Product: Cream Corn Starch
    Note: various cut out recipes
  - Sperry Standard Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0018)
    Product: Sperry Drifted Snow Flour, Bran, Baking Powder, etc.
  - The Latest Cake Secrets, 1934 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0019)
    Note: color pictures, good condition, envelope included
  - Useful Hints in Cooking, 1938 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0020)
    Company: AG Stores
    Product: AG Stores
    Note: alphabetized list of useful information, charts/informationrmation on cooking time
  - White Lily Flour…Cook Book, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0021)
    Note: cost $1.00, edited by cooking teacher Mrs. Stanfield of Atlanta, Famous Cooks in Southland Rely on White Lily
  - Wispy Light Bakings With Watkins Baking Powder… It's Double Acting!, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0022)
    Product: Watkins Baking Powder, Vanilla, Cocoa
  - Clabber Girl Recipes for Delicious Cakes, Biscuits, Hot Breads, and Other Tasty Foods, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0023)
  - Happy Times Recipe Book, 1934 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0024)
    Note: black-and-white pictures of food with chef illustrations, singing and musical notes/lyrics on cover
  - Tested Recipes Successful Baking for Flavor and Texture, 1937 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0025)
    Note: color pictures, Spokesperson Martha Lee Anderson
  - The Comical Cruises of Captain Cooky, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0026)
    Note: black-and-white illustrations on blue paper cover, rhyming story told in form of poetry between recipes
  - The Little Book of Excellent Recipes, 1934 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0027)
    Company: Davis Baking Powder
    Note: by the Mystery Chef, black-and-white illustrations, inserted color ad, two loose cutout recipes in center of booklet
  - True Fruit' Soda Fountain Requisites, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0028)
    Company: J. Hungerford Smith Company
  - A Picture Story of Tea and Coffee, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0029)
    Product: Chase & Sanborn Coffee and Tea
    Note: black-and-white pictures of Chase & Sanborn factories and headquarters
  - History of a Coffee Bean, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0030)
    Note: illustrated story about coffee, hole in middle of every page so that pic of coffee shows through
  - The Romantic Story of a Cup of Fragrant Formosa Oolong Tea, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0031)
    Product: Formosa Oolong Tea
    Note: color illustrations about tea-making
  - Appetizers, Bridge Sandwiches, Cocktail Canapés, 1935 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0032)
  - Taste Treats in Salads, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0033)
    Product: Good Luck Whipped Dressing, French Dressing
  - Wear-Ever' new method of Cooking, 1934 (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0034)
    Product: Wear-Ever utensils, pots, pans
  - Kitchen Guide, circa 1930s (Box C03, Item 1930sC-0035)
    Company: Retail Hardware Trade of America
    Product: Kitchen Hardware ?
    Note: cut out recipes taped in blank spaces for additional recipes, blue hardcover
  - Our Baker's Bake-Kups for cup cakes and muffins, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0036)
    Company: Clinton Distributors
    Product: Clinton Bake-Kups
    Note: yellow cover
  - Recipes For The Homemaker, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0037)
    Company: A. Kreamer, Inc.
    Product: Kreamerware
  - Wonder Shredder Recipes, 1931 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0038)
    Company: Dixon Prosser, Inc.
    Product: Wonder Shredder
  - Appetite Tempters from the Kraft Kitchen, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0039)
    Product: Kraft cheeses, Miracle Whip, Philadelphia Cream Cheese
  - Candies, 1934 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0040)
  - Cheese Dishes, 1934 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0041)
    Company: Extension Service of the College of Agriculture, The U of Wisconsin, Madison
    Product: Cheese Dishes
  - Dinner from Soup to Dessert made with Pet Milk, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0042)
  - Genuine Meadow Grove Brand Full Cream Cheese Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0043)
    Product: Meadow Grove Full Cream Cheese
  - Keynotes to Meal Planning, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0044)
    Company: Tillamook
    Product: Tillamook cheese
  - New and Tempting Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0045)
  - Some Sealtest Recipes, 1939 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0046)
    Product: Cheese, milk, ice cream, etc.
    Note: Ad for radio show 'Your Family and Mine'
  - Something different to do with inexpensive favorites for 2 or 4 or 6, 1935 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0047)
  - The Sealtest Food Adviser, 1939 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0048)
    Product: Sealtest Cream
    Note: color and black-and-white pictures
  - Wilson's New Recipes, Delicious new foods made with Wilson's Milk, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0049)
    Company: Wilson Milk Company
    Product: Wilson's Evaporated Milk
    Note: color pictures, foreword by Catherine Jackson
  - Bananas take a bow... in attractive new dishes for the up-to-date hostess, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0050)
    Company: Home Economics Department
  - Blue Goose Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Recipes and Information, 1930 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0051)
    Company: A. F. G. Inc.
    Product: Blue Goose fruits and vegetables
  - Morning, Noon and Night, 1934 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0052)
    Product: DOLE Hawaiian Pineapple Juice
  - Orange Salads, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0053)
    Company: Sunkist Growers, Inc.
  - Virden's Camp Fire Brand Selected California Fruits, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0054)
    Company: Virden Packing Company
    Product: Virden's Camp Fire California Canned Fruits
    Note: small booklet shaped like a can with color front and back
  - Cool-Creamy-Desserts The Junket Book, 1932 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0055)
    Company: Junket Food Products
    Product: Junket' powder
  - Creamy Ice Cream Made in Your Automatic Refrigerator or Hand Freezer… with Junket Mix, 1935 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0056)
    Product: Junket Mix
  - Elderberry Jelly Black Raspberry Jelly, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0057)
  - How to make Rennet-Custards and Ice Cream, 1938 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0058)
    Product: Junket' milk and powder
    Note: color and black-and-white pictures, silver seal on cover
  - Knox Gelatine, Desserts Salads Candies and Frozen Dishes, circa 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0059)
    Note: color illustrations, insert of two page color illustrations
  - Pies Mother Never Made, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0060)
  - Quality Gelatine Dessert… Knox Jell, 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0061)
    Product: Knox Jell
  - Taste the Good Rich Flavors of Knox Jell, 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0062)
  - Announcing Hathaway's Bakery Service to your Home, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0063)
    Company: Hathaway Bakeries
    Product: Enriched Guest Bread
  - Certified for Food Value, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0064)
    Company: Red and White Store
    Product: Kellogg's Whole Wheat Biscuit
    Note: 25 recipes on index cards in a torn envelope
  - RICE 200 Delightful ways to serve it, 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0065)
    Note: color and black-and-white pictures, recommended use of Blue Rose Rice
  - The Metropolitan Life Cook Book, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0066)
    Product: Metropolitan Life
    Note: black cover with color illustrations
  - A New Adventure In Cooking!, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0067)
    Company: Harper-Wyman Company
    Product: Harper Uni-Matic gas range
  - Coronado Electric Refrigerator Instructions and Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0068)
    Company: Coronado
  - Electric Refrigerator Recipes, circa 1930s (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0069)
    Product: Electric Refrigerator
    Note: no cover, no staples
  - How to Use the Grayson Oven Control for Economy, Convenience and Time Saving, 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0070)
  - Magic Chef Cooking, 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0071)
    Product: American Stove
    Note: color illustration inserts, worn cover, evidence of water damage
  - Making the Most of your Electrolux with practical recipes, 1935 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0072)
    Company: Electrolux Refrigerator
  - RobertShaw Cookbook, Selected recipes for time and temperature oven cooking, 1936 (Box C04, Item 1930sC-0073)
    Product: RobertShaw Oven Heat Control
    Note: black-and-white illustrations, sliver cover
  - Recipe of the Month' Magazine, 1935 (Box C05, Item 1930sC-0074)
    Company: Penn Beef Company
    Product: Cudahy's
  - 36 Thrifty Meals with Star Canned Meats, circa 1930s (Box C05, Item 1930sC-0075)
    Product: Star Canned Meats
    Note: recipes from Marie Gifford's Kitchen, small sepia colored illustrations, hole in corner of booklet